Guide to the Theatre and Dance Department records, 1937-2011 RG0084
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Videotapes, 1968-2008; RG0084 Series 5 (Film can 13, Film can 11, Box 1, Film can 12, Film can 16, Film can 17, Film can 14, Film can 15, Box 2)
  - Hostage, 2/18/1988 (Box 5)
  - Stars of the Morning Sky, Fall 1990 (Box 5)
  - HMS Pinafore, 6/4/1987 (Box 5)
  - The Good Doctor, April 1995 (Box 5)
  - Hamlet, 10/22/1992 (Box 5)
  - Dracula, 11/03/1991 (Box 5)
  - House of Blue Leaves, 4/14/1988 (Box 5)
  - Sands Cycles (Box 5)
  - On the Verge, 3/19/1990 (Box 5)
  - The Good Doctor, April 1995 (Box 5)
  - The Pirates of Penzance, June 1988 (Box 5)
  - The Runner Stumbles, 10/13/1988 (Box 5)
  - Moon over the Brewery, 10/3/1991 (Box 5)
  - Enchanted Night, 4/12/2001 (Box 5)
  - Glee club and troubadour reunion, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Viola recital, 4/25/1976 (Box 5)
- Departmental files, 1938-2003; RG0084 Series 6; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains programs, correspondence, brochures, posters, memorandums, press releases, photographs, flyers, and transcripts. They range in date from 1938 to 2003. They concern the Orchesis Dance Troupe activities, Women's Athletic Association of The George Washington University, the Washington Dance Association, dance recitals, dance symposiums, the Department of Physical Education for Women, conferences, junior Dance Group, the Department of Physical Education of Central High School, dance workshops, performances, courses in dance, artist-in-residences, Department of Human Kinetics and Leisure Studies, programs of study, history of the Theater and Dance Department, and lectures. A transcript of an oral history of Erika Thimey, "A Model for an Oral History Memoir: transcripts and videotape of a Dancer's Work" is also included.
  - Physical Education for women - Orchesis Dance Troupe activities, 1938-1943, 03/22/1938-03/17/1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Theater and Dance Department - dance - course brochures, 06/02/1952-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Theater and Dance Department - dance - event brochures/programs, 1939-1960, 03/30/1939-12/10/1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Theater and Dance Department - dance - event brochures/programs, 1961-1970, 03/18/1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Theater and Dance Department - dance - event brochures/programs, 1971-1975, 01/22/1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Theater and Dance Department - dance - event brochures/programs, 1976-1978, 04/09/1976-12/02/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Theater and Dance Department - dance - event brochures/programs, 1979, 01/07/1979-06/14/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Theater and Dance Department - dance - event brochures/programs, 1980-2003, 03/18/1980-04/23/2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Theater and Dance Department - dance - history, 03/04/1974-04/10/2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Theater and Dance Department - Model for an Oral History Memoir (Erika Thimney), 1980, 12/1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Files, 1966-2004; RG0084 Series 7; 0.5 Linear feet
  Materials in this series includes research papers, clippings, and brochures. They range in date from 1966-2004.
  - Research Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Research Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Research Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Research Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dance Program Brochures, 1966-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dance Concerts/Events-Posters, Postcards, Promotional Material, 1981-2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - International Improvisation Festival, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Senior Dance Concert, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Maida Withers, 1994-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Concert Programs, 1983-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Posters, 1979-2002; RG0084 Series 8; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Materials in this series includes posters from the Theater and Dance Department. They range in date from 1979-2002.
  - Washington Dancew View, 10/1979-11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Cover of Washington Dance View October/November 1979 Vol.1 No.1. Has picture of Nancy Galeota and has been matted. Was originally framed.
  - Sylvia's Real Good Advice, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Black and white poster of woman in bathtub.
  - Spring Dance Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Two red posters with yellow figures dancing.
  - Have A Moving Experience, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Poster for the Department of Human Kinetics and Leisure Studies.
  - Dance Concert-Student Alumni Choreography, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Black and white poster with person's arm outstretched.
  - Dance Spring '84, 04/12/1984-04/14/1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Black and white poster with black figures dancing.
  - Dance Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Red poster with male dancer.
  - The George Washington U. Student-Faculty... Dance Concert, 11/17/1983-11/19/1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Black and white poster with several dancers.
  - Dance Fall, 1981 Student-Faculty Concert, 11/20/1981-11/21/1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Black and white poster with black ink spot design.
  - Dance Spring '83, 04/21/1983-04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Black and white poster with black figure dancing.
  - Dance Concert Series, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Mauve poster.
  - Fall Dance Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Four white posters with hot pink dancers.
  - The Caucasion Chalk Circle, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Black poster with orange lettering and symbols for male and female.
  - Video Dance Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Two blue posters.
  - The Me Nobody Knows, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Blue poster with color figures dancing in front of graffitti wall.
  - Spring Dance Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Rainbow designed poster.
  - Cabaret, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Red and gray poster.
  - Fall Dance Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Red poster with black figures and colored leaves.
  - Hamlet, 10/22/1992-10/24/1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Black poster.
  - Pops, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Yellow poster.
  - Lunatics and Lovers, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Fuscia and purple poster.
  - Spring Dance Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Green poster with flowers.
  - Fall Dance Concert with guest artist Tish Carter., undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Purple and cream poster (2 posters).
  - Dracula, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Black, red, and white poster with dracula.
  - An Evening of Music and Dance, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Black and white poster.
  - Moon Over The Brewery, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Blue and white poster.
  - Eric Overmyer's On The Verge Or The Geography Of Yearning, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Two purple and green posters.
  - Fifth of July, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Student-Faculty Dance Concert, 11/19/1982-11/20/1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Cream and black poster.
  - Student-Faculty Dance Concert-Featuring Guest Artist-in-Residence Daniel McCuster & Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Dance Works, 11/20/2002-11/23/2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Mulit-colored poster.
  - Maida Withers one-woman show, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Sample certificate for Spanish Dance Society, 06/16/1986-07/03/1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Cut out certificate on matte paper.
  - Cloud Nine, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Blue and white poster with drawing of little girl on a cloud.
  - Waiting for Marge, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Two black and white posters.
  - Stars In the Morning Sky, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Black, red, and white poster.
  - In Good Company, 09/30/1993-10/02/1993 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Colorful poster.
  - Fall Dance Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Three black and white posters.
  - Fall Dance Concert, 10/31/1985-11/02/1985 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Two light blue posters.
  - Dance Faculty in Concert and Student-Faculty Dance Concert, 10/15/1982-11/20/1982 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Salmon colored poster.
  - City Dance, 05/03/1980-05/10/1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Two blue and pink posters.
  - CODA-Contemporary Dancers of Alexandria, 03/29/1980 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Red poster.
  - Twelve Days of April Festival of Performing Arts, 04/01/1987-04/12/1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Administrative records, 1990-1995; RG0084 Series 10; 0.25 Linear feet
    This series includes four folders on Memoranda, Press Releases, Flyers, and Programs. They range in date from 1990-1995.
    - Memoranda, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Flyers, 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, 1939-1996; RG0084 Series 11; 5.75 Linear feet
      This series consists of black and white photographs of individual dancers and titles/productions. There are 8 x 10 as well as oversized photographs, including some that are mounted. The photographs range in date from 1939-1996, but many have no date.
      - "Summerspace," Robert Kovich and Chris Komar pictured, photographed by Jack Mitchell, Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - "Solo," Merce Cunningham pictured, photographed by Jack Mitchell, Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - "Harbinger," Christine Sarry pictured, choreographed by Eliot Feld, photographed by Herb Migdoll, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - "Harbinger," unidentified dancers, choreographed by Eliot Feld, photographed by Herb Migdoll, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - "Mazurka," Christine Sarry and Richard Fein pictured, photographed by Lois Greenfield, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - "U.S. Lions," unidentified dancers, choreographed by Jan Van Dyke, photographed by Richard Tabor, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified dancers from the George Washington University Dance program, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified dancers from the George Washington University Dance program, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Wendy Woodson, Suzanne Callahan, and Lisa from the George Washington University Dance program, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Unidentified dancers from the George Washington University Dance program, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Jan Van Dyke, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Sara and Jerry Pearson, photographed by Otto M. Berk, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Sara and Jerry Pearson, photographed by Caravaglia, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - "Errands," Michael Kilgore and two other unidentified dancers. Also article about Arthur Bauman, choreographer of "Errands.", 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Clifford Shulman, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - People sitting on a gym floor and using various objects as musical instruments, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - "Vantage Points," Daniel McCusker and Betsy Beaven pictured, choreographed by Daniel McCusker, photographed y John D. Kramer, Ram Island Dance Company, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Heidi Geier, MFA, George Washington University, pictured with four unidentified dancers, Spring Concert, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Brian Zeigler, MFA, George Washington University, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - "Home," Heidi Geier and Skip Costa pictured, George Washington Dance Concert, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Liz Lerman, Kimberli Boyd, and Judith Jourdin, photographed by Lise Metzger, Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - "Flying Into the Middle," Liz Lerman pictured, photographed by Beatriz Schiller, Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - "Faith and Science on the Midway" (Shehechianu parts 1 & 2), Peter DiMuro, Bea Wattenberg, and Kimberli Boyd pictured, choreographed by Liz Lerman, photographed by Beatriz Schiller, Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Thomas Dwyer and Michelle Pearson, photographed by Lise Metzger, Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Thomas Dwyer and Michelle Pearson, photographed by Lise Metzger, Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Unidentified female, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Unidentified male, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Unidentified female, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Unidentified female, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Duo" (Lucia Petta and Jerry Ross), 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Master Group, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Witchcraft", 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "The Three Sisters", 1947 -1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Holiday Mood", 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Johnny Jones", 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Square Dance", 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Dance Techniques, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Dancers backstage at McKinley High School, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "The Aerialists", 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Men and Women", 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Mutt and Jeff", 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "A Young Man's Fancy, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Blues", 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Dance Technique, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Military Ball", 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Abstractions", 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Facades", 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "The Queen's Conscience", 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Boulevard of the Abnormal", 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Modern Fantasy", 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Dance Techniques, 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Dance Techniques, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "God's Trombone", 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Mother and Two Eligible Daughters", 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Ponytails and Crazy Pants", 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Carrousel from CARNIVAL", 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: "Ziccary Zeven", 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Unidentified female, 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Elizabeth Burtner, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Elizabeth Burtner and Jerry Ross, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: University of Maryland - unidentified female, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Fremont Davis photographs: Unidentified male and female, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Oversize photographs: Three 12.5" x 11" black and white photographs of Michael Kilgore performing a work choreographed by Judith Dunn, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Oversize photographs: Impressions Dance Concert Poster, April 14, 15 - 7.25" x 9" black and white photograph of an unidentified dancer mounted on pressboard, signed by "Brooke.", undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Audiotapes, 1974-1995; RG0084 Series 9; 0.25 Linear feet (Flat box 1)
  Materials in this series includes audiotapes, featuring people such as Martha Graham, Jan Van Dyke, and Merce Cunningham. They range in date from 1974-1995.
  - Gregory Peck talking about M. Graham, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Interview: Jan Van Dyke - N.d. Johnson, 03/11/1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Interview with Lix Lerman, 04/13/1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - George Jackson, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Text on paper with audiotape: "call 5/21-noon George Jackson 245-1465 (w) 488-8635 (H) May 29th at 12:30-"
  - Interview with Walter Terry, 01/1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Text on audiotape: "Interview with Walter Terry 1/79" Text on paper with audiotape: "Interview with Walter Terry 1976" Note change in date. Uncertain on which date is correct.
  - G.W.U. Elliott, 12/29/1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Florence Pennella, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Text with audiotape: "Florence Pennella 523-5712 5/21 - 6:00 Marrin"
  - Interview with Cliff Keuter, 04/07/1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anne Marie Welsh Interview, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Text with tapes: "Anne Marie Welsh 5/14 Interview 2 tapes." Two audiotapes
  - Unlabelled tape, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cunningham & Cage Part II, 02/10/1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Unlabelled tape, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dick Cavett interview of Merce Cunningham, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Jan Murray, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Text with tape: "Jan Murray 301-435-1766 (H) 5/19 11:30 Peabody"
  - Interview with Walter Terry, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Interview with Susan Farrell sides 1(A) & 3(B), 09/17/1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Interview with Susan Farrell sides 2(A), 09/16/1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Burtner Tape 1 side 1 & 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Text with tape:"Jean Nordhams 543-1905 Fri 5/18 2:00-Marvin"
  - Burtner Tape 2 3rd side, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Maybe interview with Florence Pennella, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chrystelle Bond, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Text with tape:"Chrystelle Bond 301-825-3300 6/2 Goucher-Baltimore 11:00"
  - Minimal Art Rainer-Lecture 18 Tape 15, 04/01/1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Judson Lecture-George Jackson-Lecture 21 Tape 16, 04/22/1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dance in Education-Lecture 16 Tape 13, 03/25/1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Administrative files of Maida Withers, Professor of Dance, 1961-1993; 1967-1980; Series 12; Withers, Maida; 6 Linear Feet 4 record cartons
  The records in this series are the files of GW Professor of Dance, Maida Withers. Materials include information about the Dance Production Groups, dancer portfolios, flyers, posters, programs, publicity, photographs, photographic negatives, contact sheets, correspondence, and syllabi. Materials in this series date between 1961 and 1993, with the bulk of the material dating from 1967 to 1980.
  Arrangement
  This series is unprocessed and is in the order received.
  Dance schools; Dancers; Dance companies; Dance
  - Flyers, 1976-1977; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Flyers, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flyers, 1966-1967; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Flyers, 1967-1968; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Flyers, 1970-1971; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Flyers, 1968-1969; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Flyers, 1969-1970; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - MA in Education, Specialty in Dance, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Flyers, 1975-1976; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Flyers, 1978-1979; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, 1977-1978; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dance Production Groups Constitution, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Flyers, 1980-1981; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dance Production Groups, 1967-1968; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dance Production Groups publicity, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dance Production Groups, 1967; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dance Production Groups Fall, 1980; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Summer Dance Workshops, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - GW Student/Faculty Concert, 11/07/1980-11/08/1980; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Flyers, 1974-1975; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Flyers, 1971-1972; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Flyers, 1972-1973; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Flyers, 1973-1974; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pauline Koner Master Lessons, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dance Production Groups Photographs, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dance Production Groups Photographs, circa 1966-1967; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dance Production Groups Photographs, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dance Production Groups, 1974-1975; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Concert Programs, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Dance Production Groups Current Business, 1981-1982; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Dance Production Groups--Budget, 1979; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Forms, 1982; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Dance Production Groups Workstudy, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Dance Production Groups, 1979-1980; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Resumes--Guest Artists, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Dance Production Groups, 1981; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Michael Kasper Concert, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dance Production Groups programs, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Newspaper articles, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Guest Artists, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Sharon Sheehan, undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Dance Production Groups Photographs, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Terry Fox, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut students, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bella Livdsky, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Meredith Monk, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Villiage Voice, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - History/Dance Notation, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, Programs, Press Kits, 1961-1976; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Interview with Video Artist Elliot Caplan, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Clippings on Limon, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Modern Dance Personalities, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Costumes for Dance--Thesis--Carol Ann Davis, 1983; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Program, photographs, sketches, syllabus, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ubu Roi (1896), undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dance Production Groups, 1968-1969; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dance Flyers, GWU Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Programs, Syllabi, Path Dance Co. portfolio, Photographs, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Dance Programs Departments, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Dance Production Groups, undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Contact sheets--photographs, 1970-1971; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Deborah Slater, 1970-1971; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Dance Production Groups--Memos, Correspondence, 1984-1985; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Programs, dance portfolios, flyers, 1967-1985; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Sara Shelton, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Douglas Dunn, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Norman Walker, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Rod Rogers, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Edith Stephan Co., undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Rudy Perez, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Daniel Nagrin, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Martha Graham--clipping, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Glenn Tetly--clipping, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Paul Taylor, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1967-1968; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Local Dance Companies and Schools, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - PECW, 1968; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dance Schools and Workshops, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Avant Garde, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dance Education History, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Al Huang, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Tap Dancing, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Art Bauman, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 19)